(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-30T21:58:42.442636",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
BAU BAU!
Welcome to 3rd anniversary and celebration of Hololive!
It's thanks to Haachama-senpai that we're standing here!
Here we go!
RED HEART!
1, 2, 3, go!
Hi, how are you? Are you calling up my phone?
Baby, tell me what is wrong, don't you ever let me go
Hi, I am good, I am still looking for proof
Am I good enough for you? Don't you tell me what's my rule
This is me, are you coming on the ride?
We are going super high
Got to be who what I like
You and me, are you ready for the fight?
Alright, alright, alright!
Stronger than I ever been before
This is who I am
Nothing in the way
...and far away
You and me, we make the part of me
I give you my big red heart
My, my big red heart
I'll be true to my big red heart
My red heart
Hi, over there
Thank you for coming along
On this journey of my own
Promise me you won't let go
Yes, this is me
I am falling, but I'm strong
'Cause you got me in your arms
Don't you ever let me go
I want you to come with me on the ride
This is going super high
I am falling from the sky
Got to be who you wanna be, that's right
Alright, alright, alright
Let's go!
1, 2, 3, 4!
I am still a girl
Figuring out what's true or false in this whole wide world
I'm your only girl
Tell me once more what's really going on with you
I'm looking for the right one on the road
The one that'll always take me back to you
This can be home
Will you be my home?
Stronger than I've ever been before
This is who I am
Nothing in the way
Today and far away
You and me, we make the part of me
I give you my big red heart
My, my big red heart
I'll be true to my big red heart
はい！ Thank you so much, Ruffians, for coming to...
Yes! Thank you so much, Ruffians, for coming to...
...FUWAMOCO's 3rd Anniversary Live, Thanks to hololive!
Thanks to hololive!
FUWAMOCOの3周年記念ライブ...
For FUWAMOCO's 3rd Anniversary Live...
...Thanks to hololiveに来てくれて本当にありがとう！
...thank you so much for coming to Thanks to hololive!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Today, our entire concert...
...is to share our love and appreciation for hololive,
our senpai, senmates, kouhai...
...and YOU!
そう！今日、3周年を記念して...
That's right! Today, to celebrate our 3rd anniversary...
今日はhololiveへの思いと感謝の気持ちを伝えるために...
...and to convey our feelings and gratitude towards hololive...
思いっきり歌って踊りまーす！
...we're going to sing and dance with all our might!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
And this stream is going to be packed with ALL of our love for hololive!
Get ready, okay?
And...
...of course, you do want to know...
...our hashtag, right? Yeah! Very important!
Our hashtag for today is #FWMC3rd!
Yeah!
Please take lots of screenshots, pasha-pasha,
and tweet about us on SNS, okay?
そう！ハッシュタグは#FWMC3rdで...
That's right! Use the hashtag #FWMC3rd...
...スクリーンショットをたくさんSNSに投稿してね！
...and post lots of screenshots on SNS!
見てるよー！
We'll be watching!
Yeah, Pero is looking, like...
Ooh, Pero, what are you doing?
Ooh, what do you have to say?
Okay! Yeah, we're reading!
But our very first song that we performed was Haachama-senpai's RED HEART!
RED HEART, you know, it's a very precious song of hers.
And you know, it's because of Haachama-senpai that actually FUWAMOCO...
...we found hololive!
そう！FUWAMOCOね、はぁちゃま先輩のおかげでhololiveに出会いましたから...
That's right! Because of Haachama-senpai, FUWAMOCO discovered hololive...
...とってもとっても大切な曲です！
...so it's a very, very special song to us!
We love you so much, Haachama-senpai!
We're waiting to collab again, okay?
We want to cook together, okay?
はぁちゃま先輩大好きだー！
We love you, Haachama-senpai!
バウバウ！バウバウ！バウバウ！
Bau bau! Bau bau! Bau bau!
And, look at this stage!
It was designed, today's stage, a very special hololive-themed stage!
Today's stage was designed as a very special hololive-themed stage!
You got that right!
そう！今回のステージはホロライブをテーマに作ってもらいました！
Yeah! This time's stage was made with a Hololive theme!
We really hope that our love for hololive will reach you today!
Yeah, we'll be singing and dancing, of course! At a very special stage, right? So please look forward to it!
Yeah, we'll be singing and dancing, of course, on a very special stage! So please look forward to it!
And...
There might be a big announcement, too!
そう！そしてそして、重大発表もあるから、まだまだ最後まで見てください！
Yes! And there's also a major announcement, so please keep watching until the very end!
So please watch to the very end, okay? Stay tuned!
アドベントのみんな！
Everyone from Advent!
Happy anniversary for the world!
Happy anniversary to the world!
Happy anniversary!
アドベントのみんながお祝いに来てくれました！
Everyone from Advent came to celebrate with us!
Thank you!
We just celebrated our 3rd anniversary with a lot of you a few weeks ago...
It was such a fun time! But now, we're in a booth here!
Welcome! Oh my god!
Well, before it's time to have an announcement, you know...
Well, before it's time for the announcement...
Shiori, you have anything to say?
Shiori, do you have anything to say?
Happy 3rd anniversary!
It's been really nuts if you think about it...
...because we've had the evolution of getting to know each other from the very first collab game to now 3 years later, we gift each other little silly gifts like gnomes, a little cute plushie, a bookmark...
...because of the evolution of getting to know each other from our very first collab game, to now 3 years later giving silly gifts like gnomes, plushies, bookmarks...
...and I just really appreciate being everyone's friend. Let's be friends for many more years to come!
...and I really appreciate being everyone's friend. Let me be friends for many more years to come!
Nerissa!
Well, of course, it's FuwaMoco Day, so I'll mostly be talking about you, but keep in mind I do feel this way about all of Advent, but it's applicable to everyone!
Well, of course, it's FuwaMoco Day, so I'll mostly talk about you, but keep in mind I feel this way about all of Advent!
You know, since we all got together, it's just been so clear that all of us were meant to be friends, if you know what I mean.
Since we all got together, it's just been so clear that all of us were meant to be friends, if you know what I mean.
Like, I truly can't imagine being in a gen with more hardworking and amazing people than you guys...
...and every day I'm just so, so grateful to be able to have you guys here as my friends and as my genmates. I'm so happy!
...and every day I'm just so grateful to have you guys as my friends and genmates. I'm so happy!
3周年おめでとうございます！
Happy 3rd Anniversary!
Touch me again! Wow!
Oh, what if I touch your horns? Scary, scary!
Bijou!
Okay, let me hold your paws while I say this.
FuwaMoco, 3周年おめでとうございます！
FuwaMoco, happy 3rd anniversary!
You know, we've been through so much together as Advent, and whether it's you guys, you know...
We've been through so much together as Advent, and whether it's you guys...
...like you fed me boba, you got me a microphone, you made sure I didn't die...
...like you fed me boba, got me a microphone, made sure I didn't die...
...you held my hands as I crossed the street...
...you held my hand as I crossed the street...
...and I couldn't imagine starting this journey with anybody else other than you guys!
So I'm so happy we're here celebrating together!
It's really been an amazing 3 years!
You know, but... We love you!
Let's continue strong together!
But you know, our concert is only just started, right?
But you know, our concert has only just started, right?
We get to sing together, the five of us, you know?
Well, FuwaMoco wanted to sing a song that means so much to us.
Without our senpais' hard work, we wouldn't be here, you know?
And when we all debuted, there were 5 senpais that were just about to celebrate their 3rd anniversary, too!
So, with all the love and respect in our hearts, please listen to this very special version of hololive English -Myth-'s original song!
Here we go!
ReUnion!
Sing out boldly again,
continuing this odyssey.
We'll start this new refrain brimming with memories!
And when the clouded skies become bright, let's reunite!
Ready? Set? Stream!
It's almost showtime, I would say.
It's not tomorrow, it's today!
But when times are ruff, is it really enough?
'Cause they're chasing me endlessly, why?
Take it easy, what have we learned?
When the Cell doors open, it's our turn!
We can do this, call the Adventrix!
Teach new dogs all of our old tricks.
Been on the run for so long that we really hit our stride.
Now look at all we've accomplished together side by side!
Dreamers to streamers to entertainers to senpai!
Justice can't catch us!
"Mocojan, behind you!" "Bau!"
Spanning new dimensions, we can bring another mystery to light!
Planning our ascension, dancing in flight, we ignite...
Through the stories we inspire, we can light another fire, Advent's reaching even higher!
Through this world and beyond, our distant dreams have brought us here.
A strong, unyielding bond, guiding us endlessly, will bring us moments that we hold dear.
Time rushes on; and though these winds may scatter us,
we'll keep this promise:
When the moment's finally right, we'll always find a way to reunite!
I'll lend a helping paw, I can go the extra mile,
I'm gonna give my all, so let's protect your smile! Bau!
I'm rocking in again, now I'll never break my streak!
Gaming streams full of memes six or seven times a week! Yeah!
It's time for a pup talk, 'cause I know it's essential,
that even when we're in the doghouse, we got endless potential!
It's time for pawsitive thoughts, so I keep on pondering donuts,
but now I'm getting warm and fuzzy from the love that you've shown us! Bau Bau!
Countless moments led us to this day:
triumph and sorrow, hope for tomorrow —
we'll always find our way, come what may!
In every universe, we were always meant to meet.
I'll lead a boundless search. We will never know defeat!
My wings will guide your hands as the fateful days go by,
we will cut a path through a never-ending sky!
Shining bright together, I can sense another wish is coming true.
We'll be friends fur-ever, loyal and true, me and you!
Sing out again! The clouded skies give way to clear;
we'll start this new refrain brimming with memories!
Another story's starting right here...
We'll keep forging ahead to make a saga all our own.
Whichever paths we tread, steadily journeying, we know we're never really alone —
if we believe wherever fate may find us,
our love will bind us,
every epic chapter we write will set us on the path to reunite!
Step and Go!!
昨日から止まったような
As if time had stopped since yesterday
時計を押さない
I won't press the clock
炎の音 思い出して
Remembering the sound of the flame
もし失敗になっていいよ
Even if it ends in failure, it's alright.
あの優しい声が側にあったから
Because that gentle voice was by my side.
不意に傷ついて 道に迷った日もあったけれど
Though there were days I was suddenly hurt and lost my way,
いつだって探していたのは
What I was always looking for...
輝けるはずの Better day
...was a better day that was meant to shine!
Every day 解き放て ためらいがちなそのエモーション
Everyday, unleash that emotion you tend to hesitate with!
時代の正義にしたって つまらないよ
Following the justice of the times is so boring!
Every day 君であれ 立ち止まる日もあるけれど
Everyday, be yourself; though there are days you stand still,
ねぇ きっと君は大丈夫
Hey, I'm sure you'll be alright.
Step and Go!
誰もが記憶の中に
Everyone has inside their memories...
ある大事なあの笑顔 抱きしめている
...that precious smile they keep holding close.
いつか君にまた会いたいなら
If I want to meet you again someday,
素直にちゃんと気持ち伝えたい
I want to convey my feelings properly and honestly.
自分自身で引いたボーダーラインなら さあ飛び越えて
If it's a borderline you drew yourself, come on, jump over it!
いつだって描いていこうよ 君らしい色で
Let's always draw it out in your own unique color.
Better day
Every day 煌めいて 今動き出したエモーション
Everyday, sparkle! The emotion that has now begun to move,
誰かの正義にしたって つまらないよ
Following someone else's justice is so boring!
Every day らしくあれ やがてこの雨も上がって
Everyday, be like yourself; eventually this rain will stop too.
ねぇ きっと君は大丈夫
Hey, I'm sure you'll be alright.
Step and Go!
いろんな風が吹くだけ 涙は出るけれど
Different winds blow, and tears may fall,
止まない雨はないように
But just like how no rain falls forever...
君ならできるよ Step and Go!
...you can do it! Step and Go!
Every day 解き放て ためらいがちなそのエモーション
Everyday, unleash that emotion you tend to hesitate with!
時代の正義にしたって つまらないよ
Following the justice of the times is so boring!
Every day 君であれ 立ち止まる日もあるけれど
Everyday, be yourself; though there are days you stand still,
ねぇ きっと君は大丈夫
Hey, I'm sure you'll be alright.
Step and Go!
FuwaMocoの居場所である大好きなhololiveを作ってくれてありがとう
Thank you for creating Hololive, our beloved place where FuwaMoco belongs!
でりぃ〜だいありぃ〜！
Daily Diary!
届けちゃおう！
Let me deliver it!
青春実況中
Youth live commentary in progress!
挑戦配信中
Challenge stream in progress!
青春実況中
Youth live commentary in progress!
挑戦配信中
Challenge stream in progress!
宝物ね 楽しいわ
It's a treasure, it's so fun!
発見！また新しい「好き」が見つかったよ
Discovery! I found a new "like" again!
ねぇねぇ 超気になる！
Hey, hey, I'm super curious!
近所にできたカフェの
The cake at the café that opened nearby...
ケーキ なんかすっごく美味しかったんだよ
...was somehow super delicious!
服のサイズになっちゃうよ！
You're gonna go up a clothing size!
知らなかったゲームや
Games I didn't know about...
聞いたことない歌
...and songs I've never heard before...
ちょっと気になったら 手を出せちゃう
...if I get a little curious, I'll just give them a try!
ほらね 一緒に遊ぼう！
See? Let's play together!
10連ガチャ
10-pull gacha!
引いてみよう (欲しい)
Let's try pulling 10 gachas! (I want it!)
ホラーゲームやってみよう (絶叫)
Let's try playing a horror game! (Screaming)
あの曲歌ってみよう (感動)
Let me try singing that song! (Moving)
全部がもう楽しいの！
Everything is just so much fun!
窓の向こうの
To the smiles...
笑顔に手を振っちゃう
...on the other side of the window, I wave!
アニメ
Anime...
視聴中
...currently watching!
発見！
Discovered!
モブのキャラに隠せるポテンシャル
The potential hidden in a background character!
(ヤバ、見る目あるわー)
(Wow, you've got an eye for this!)
知名度ない番外
An obscure spin-off,
名作見つけた新ネタ (爆笑)
I found a masterpiece, new joke! (LOL)
当たらない天気予報もきっと
Even an inaccurate weather forecast will surely...
面白いことになるんだよ
...turn into something funny!
(配信)
(Stream!)
聞いて聞いて 今朝の朝 (何？)
Listen, listen, this morning... (What?)
目覚まし鳴らなくって (何で？)
My alarm didn't ring! (Why?)
寝過ごしちゃったのは (教えて)
The reason I overslept... (Tell us!)
昨晩の生放送
...was last night's livestream!
すごく楽しくて
It was so fun...
寝つけなかったんだ (残念)
...I couldn't fall asleep! (Too bad)
特別すごいことなんて起こらないリアル
Real life where nothing particularly amazing happens,
だけどそのエッセンス 仮想の世界
but with its essence, in a virtual world,
夢に変えて 毎日がパラダイス
turned into dreams, every day is paradise!
思い切り遊んで笑っちゃおう
Let me play with all my heart and laugh!
(大正解)
(Big win!)
全部無くす覚悟してきた
I came prepared to lose everything!
(何それー)
(What's that about?)
負ける気はしないんだって
I don't feel like losing at all!
諦めたら実況終了だよ
If you give up, the commentary is over!
(えー、まだ終わりたくない)
(Eh, I don't want it to end yet!)
どんな毎日も楽しくなっちゃうんだ
Every day turns into so much fun!
出せる？ 意地出せる？
Can you show it? Can you show your guts?
ほら あなたが待ってるの
Look, everyone is waiting for you!
みんなで毎日を (一緒に)
Every day with everyone... (Together!)
出会えた嬉しさを (行こう)
The joy of having met... (Let's go!)
みんなと一緒に (いっせーの)
Together with everyone... (Ready, set...)
気分はね もう最高潮
...our mood is already at its peak!
窓の向こうの笑顔に手を振って
Wave your hand to the smiles on the other side of the window,
配信で届ける『ていり～だいあり～！』
delivering "Daily Diary!" through the stream!
せ～しゅん実況中！ (いろいろ)
Youth, currently streaming! (All kinds of things)
ちょ～せん配信中！ (試して)
Challenge, currently live! (Try it out)
せ～しゅん実況中！ (いっぱい)
Youth, currently streaming! (Lots of it)
ちょ～せん配信中！ (遊ぼう)
Challenge, currently live! (Let me play)
ていり～だいあり～！
Daily Diary!
届けよう！
Let's deliver it!
みんな大～すきっだよー！！ 3年分のDaily Diaryをみんなと一緒に作りあげたのは最高の宝物
[On-screen text: We love you all so much!! Creating 3 years' worth of Daily Diary together with everyone is our greatest treasure]
BAU BAU!
And that was "Daily Diary"!
We were really happy to perform together with Miko-senpai, Korone-senpai, and Watame-senpai!
BAU BAU!
But the reason why we chose "Daily Diary"... is because...
"Daily Diary" is a really special song to us!
We listened to it lots and lots before our debut!
And we really, really, truly wanted to try creating...
...our own Daily Diary together with Ruffians!
Also, listening to it over and over, we kept imagining what that might look like!
そう、フワモコにとって『Daily Diary』はすごく大切な曲で...
Yes, to FUWAMOCO, "Daily Diary" is a very special song,
デビュー前にたくさん聴いてた曲です！
and it's a song we listened to a lot before our debut!
その頃の気持ちはまだすごく覚えてて...
We still remember how we felt back then very clearly,
「早くデビューしてみんなとのDaily Diaryを作りたい！」って...
thinking, "I want to debut soon and create a Daily Diary with everyone!"
ね、しょうがなかったんですね！
Right, we couldn't help but feel that way!
でも、この3年間でみんなと作ってきた思い出が、想像以上に素晴らしいDaily Diaryになってるよ！
But the memories we've made with everyone over these 3 years have become an even more wonderful Daily Diary than we imagined!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
You know, to be making together an even more wonderful Daily Diary than we could have ever imagined, you know?
Thank you all so much!
BAU BAU!
Ah, ah, ah!
You know, I think we still have a lot more coming up, including...
...one more corner!
A super duper BIG announcement!
It's really important, okay?
重大告知まであと少しだよ！
The major announcement is coming up very soon!
忘れちゃいけないよね！
You shouldn't forget about it, right?
Yeah, you cannot miss it, okay? So make sure you stay with us until the very end!
But we still have some very special songs to perform for you!
Hehehe...
I'm a little nervous, Mococo-chan!
I'm nervous, too!
Well... let's get ready, Mococo-chan!
Okay! Let's get going! Okay?
BAU BAU! BAU BAU!
君のヒロインは誰
Who is your heroine?
覚えてる？ 優しさ
Do you remember? That kindness...
君の言葉にキュンとして
My heart fluttered at your words...
上手に言えない
I can't express it well,
代わりにウインクかけてみたの
so I tried winking at you instead.
目があった気がした それだけで
I felt like our eyes met, and just from that,
鼓動跳ねた お願い 勘違いじゃない
my heart beat fast; please let it not be a misunderstanding.
ありませんように
May it not be so.
そっと心の中で熱い視線送った
I quietly sent a passionate gaze from my heart.
振り向いてて 願い叶っちゃった
Please turn around—and my wish came true!
ヒロインオーディション エントリーしたら私
If I enter the heroine audition,
ねぇ選んでくれるかな
hey, will you choose me?
真面目のせい？ 隠す
Is it because I'm so earnest? Hiding it...
おはようだけで伝わるよ
Just saying "good morning" conveys it.
何気ないつぶやき
A casual whisper...
もしかして期待してる？
Could it be that I'm hoping?
眩しい素敵の人ばかりで
Surrounded by dazzling, wonderful people,
自信もなくて それでも本音では
I lack confidence, but deep down inside...
365日もっと近づきたい
365 days a year, I want to get closer.
私なりのペースになるけど
Even if it's at my own pace...
ヒロインオーディション 勇気を出したら君は
In the heroine audition, if I summon my courage,
ねぇ答えてくれるかな
hey, will you respond to me?
出会った一瞬でかなりすごいミラクル
The moment we met was quite an incredible miracle.
このチャンスは赤い糸
This chance is our red thread of fate.
ギュッと手繰り寄せて 運命にしよう
Let me pull it tight and make it our destiny.
信じてまっすぐ せーので言葉にして
Believing straight ahead, let's say it together on three.
君のヒロインは誰
Who is your heroine?
きっと君の心 動かしてみせるよ
I'll definitely move your heart!
まだまだぜんぶ足りないけど
Even though I'm still lacking in so many ways...
ヒロインオーディション 選んでそして私を
In the heroine audition, choose me, and then...
いつかギュッとしてほしい
I want you to hold me tight someday.
ありがとうずっと大好きだよ
Thank you, I'll love you forever!
アキロゼ先輩の声とお歌が大好き♡ いつか二人で歌おうね！！ BAU BAU！！
[Message] "I love Aki-roze senpai's voice and singing♡ Let's sing together someday!! BAU BAU!!"
もういいじゃん ムキになっちゃって
Forget it already, getting so worked up.
カッコつけて カッコよくない
Trying to act cool, but it's not cool at all.
そういうの嫌になってんだ
I'm sick and tired of stuff like that.
ほっといてよ 知りたくない
Leave me alone, I don't want to know.
もういいじゃん やけになってんの？
Forget it already, are you being desperate?
嫉妬したり じっとできない
Getting jealous, unable to sit still.
聞こえないよう 耳塞いだって
Even if I cover my ears so I can't hear,
言ってくるじゃん しんどいなあ
you still come and say it, it's so exhausting.
僕は誰も覗かないよ
I won't pry into anyone's business.
だから僕のことそっとしておいて
So please just leave me alone.
うざいだけのバカにハイハイハイ
Say "yeah yeah yeah" to the annoying fools.
ウケるまたのお越し待ってるね
"Hilarious, looking forward to your next visit."
だとか本当は怯えてる
Saying that, but actually terrified inside.
吠えるだけの弱虫だったった
Just a coward who does nothing but bark.
痛いくせに耐えてハイハイハイ
Enduring it even though it hurts, "yeah yeah yeah".
いつも平気なフリばっかなの
Always just pretending to be fine.
僕は壁を貼ったまま笑う
I laugh with my walls built up high.
それ以上近づかないでって
Saying "don't come any closer than that."
怖いじゃん
It's scary, isn't it?
ばかばっか
Nothing but fools.
やだ ばかばっか
No way, nothing but fools.
もういいじゃん まだ怒ってんの
Forget it already, are you still mad?
ほっといてよ ホッとできない
Leave me alone, I can't feel at peace.
見ないように目を逸らしたって
Even if I look away so I don't see,
付いてくるじゃん やっぱり
you still follow me after all.
転がったら起きればいいじゃん
If you fall down, just get back up, right?
失ったら探せばいいじゃん
If you lose something, just look for it, right?
イヤイヤイヤイヤイヤイヤイヤ
No no no no no no no!
それでよくない？
Isn't that fine?
間違ったら直せばいいじゃん
If you make a mistake, just fix it, right?
やんなったらやめればいいじゃん
If you get sick of it, just quit, right?
イヤイヤイヤイヤイヤイヤイヤ
No no no no no no no!
それでよくない？
Isn't that fine?
...ないよ
...not.
だから僕のこと放っといて
So just leave me alone.
嫌なこと全部大丈夫だと言えたらいいのにな
I wish I could say everything bad is alright,
思えたらいいのにな
I wish I could truly believe that.
信号が赤だったら雨なら大正解
If the light is red or if it rains, it's a great excuse.
いつも僕はそんな論理なの
I'm always clinging to logic like that.
また言いたいこと殺したからもう忘れてくれ
I killed what I wanted to say again, so just forget it.
うわっはっはー！ ダサいだけのバカにハイハイハイ受けるー
Bwahaha! Complies with uncool fools, yeah yeah yeah, hilarious!
またのお越し待ってるねーだとか本当は怯えてる
Saying 'Looking forward to seeing you again,' but actually terrified,
吠えるだけの弱虫だったった
Just a coward who only barks.
痛いくせに耐えてハイハイハイ いつも平気なフリばっかりなのは
Enduring even when it hurts, yeah yeah yeah, always pretending to be fine.
僕は壁を貼ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないで
I laugh while keeping my guard up, don't get any closer.
どうか
Please,
本当バカバカいい加減わ とんだバグばっか出せ出せ
Seriously foolish, enough already, spitting out absurd bugs.
そんな言葉ばっかも僕もやっぱりどうしようもないバッテン少女か
Are both those words and I just hopeless, marked with an X?
正解の答えが得られないない 死ねるって僕の口バッカだね
Can't get a correct answer, talking about dying—my mouth is so stupid.
今日も壁を貼ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないでって
Today again I laugh with my wall up, saying 'Don't come any closer.'
怖いジャン
Because it's terrifying.
バカバッカ
Nothing but fools.
ほら
Look,
バカバッカ
nothing but fools.
きゅーびっと。
[Title: Cyu-pit.]
ちゅちゅちゅちゅー...
Chu-chu-chu-chuu...
何気ない声がそわそわ ちょっと遅めがいいな まだまだだって
A casual voice makes me restless, I want it a bit later, saying 'not yet.'
いつからかそれが眩しくなる
Since when did that start looking so dazzling?
気づいてんじゃない？ きっと甘いそんな言葉で Yeah
Haven't you noticed? Surely with such sweet words, yeah.
防波堤作っちゃって 丁寧に打ち抜いて
Building up a breakwater, neatly shooting right through.
だから今 落ちてく飛んでく何か 急いで転んで 渦巻く恋に仕返して
So now something falls and flies, hurrying and tumbling, paying back this swirling love.
あぁ もう君は最高だ 叶わないな
Ah, you're already the best, I'm no match for you.
君のキューピッドです 今夜夢中チュウ
I'm your Cupid, crazy in love tonight.
きっと夢に出てくる ちゅちゅちゅちゅー
I'll surely appear in your dreams, chu-chu-chu-chuu.
ちゅちゅちゅちゅー ちゅちゅちゅちゅー
Chu-chu-chu-chuu...
痛いたのよ今も
It still hurts even now.
キュンキュンです また夢中ちょっと何なんだって来る
My heart goes flutter, captivated again, wondering what this feeling is.
キュキュキュキュン キュキュキュキュン キュキュキュキュン
Kyu-kyu-kyu-kyun...
ギュッと抱きしめて
Hold me tight.
どうして
Why?
ラッタッタ ラッタッタ...
Ra-ta-ta...
君はまだ知らない事情 私も見えてないでしょう
Circumstances you don't know yet, I probably can't see them either.
なっちゃった なっちゃった...
It happened...
あの子には見せちゃう微笑 思ってみるだけで熱上昇
Showing a smile to that girl, just thinking about it makes my temperature rise.
あいらぶしょー そのまなざし
I love show, that gaze.
あぁ 探し続けた宝石みたい
Ah, like the jewel I've been searching for.
でもまだ まだ 気づくのはピンチだ 浮気する私を愛して 惚れやすく私を愛して
But realizing it now is a crisis, love me even if I'm fickle, love me even if I fall in love easily.
あぁ もう私最高だ やめられないから
Ah, I'm already the best, because I can't stop.
君のキューピッドです また夢中チュウ
I'm your Cupid, crazy in love again.
もっと欲しくなってく ちゅちゅちゅちゅー
Craving it more and more, chu-chu-chu-chuu.
ちゅちゅちゅちゅー ちゅちゅちゅちゅー
Chu-chu-chu-chuu...
期待をしちゃうよ
I'm building up expectations.
If you love 感情 注入 ずっと気持ち溢れる
If you love, injecting feelings, emotions overflowing constantly.
キュキュキュキュン キュキュキュキュン キュキュキュキュン
Kyu-kyu-kyu-kyun...
ギュッと抱きしめて
Hold me tight.
あぁ もう隠せないけど 止まらない鼓動
Ah, I can't hide it anymore, this unstoppable heartbeat.
夢から覚めて 気づいて今
Wake up from the dream and realize it now.
Went right through
Those nights, I'll never find my way back to...
inside this labyrinth of lights
there was madness
in the meaning
never laughless
we were screaming at the top of our lungs
to the numbness
this city never died
I'll fly
no proof
those heights
I'll never find another chance to say "hey, thanks for saving my life"
I was hopeless
it was stinging
running roadless
we were singing at the top of our lungs
to the numbness
this city never died
What was the root of it all? I couldn't say
Used to jump and then fall, rugged and cliched
Would shrug it off without complaint, not a sound
No use in trying to find friends, 'cause in the end nobody sticks around
It's when you shoved yourself into a crowded place
That you turned around and found yourself in love in outer space
Cue the reckless nights, no strings, laughing at our own dreams
Just what the hell was so funny?
Bark up the wrong tree, stumble, used to falling great heights
Amidst a concrete jungle, singing 'cause it felt right
We mixed the ennui and troubles rhyming our discontent
And though it's history, I can't forget the time that we spent
Convinced that this could mean another end
Exists between real and pretend
A twisted alter-fiction where I missed my chance, did not ascend and
Disappearing into the mist of "never happened"
Is the me that I can never befriend
And let it go...
Fade in, fade out
This crazy dream
Without a direction
floating aimlessly
There's nothing left
back there for me
Breathe in, but it won't stop the rain from pouring
We'd run
right through
those nights
I'll never find my way back to you inside this labyrinth of lights
There was madness
in the meaning
never laughless
We were screaming at the top of our lungs
to the numbness
This city never died
But was there ever a soul inside?
Chasing fireflies
between the soaring high-rises
Left a trail behind
defined it "wasted time of our lives"
Silent singer, overworked and underpaid
Thinks an office is a coffin until off is where you're laid
Yet a thought persists, an optimist who ought to be afraid
Saw the "nothing wrong" in writing songs behind the lonely shade
Is the world a sadder place without the words that you conveyed?
When the ladder fell and shattered every bar that we had played
Does it matter in the end the sound diminished and decayed
And your friends grew tired of fantasy, you're wishing they had stayed?
You don't get to say "I miss you"
You watched your heroes fade
Into the rear-view mirror of the villain you portrayed
Stop the pity party, listen, you don't get to be dismayed
You don't get to be emotional, feel blessed you got it made
These the best of years of life because you chose to make a trade
Recollect the days you hoped and you prayed for this
What is there to miss?
Fade in, fade out
This hazy dream
Without a direction
roaming aimlessly
There's nothing left
back there for me
Pretend it's the end of a made-up story
I'll fly
no proof
those heights
I'll never find another chance to say "hey, thanks for saving my life"
I was hopeless
it was stinging
driving roadless
we were singing at the top of our lungs
to the numbness
this city never died
I'll say goodbye to the soul inside
And yet somehow
there was romance
in our self-hate
"We've got no chance"
in this light maze
But let's hold hands
through the night haze
We'll run so fast
'til the school chime
'til the train runs
We know it's time
We're the sane ones
Waking up now
to the real life
Lemme daydream
'til the next night
I'll keep waiting
I'll keep waiting for you
It was the trade of a lifetime, but we won't forget the past!! We're so thankful! ♡ Thank you for being a senpai + friend who has shown us the way and continues to inspire us!!
Waking up now to my real life
Lemme daydream 'til the next flight
Drowning so long, I got older
Now the crowd's gone, is it over?
Is it over?
一途ってトレンド♡
[New Song: Trend of Devotion♡]
さて 教えましょう 粋な恋のルールを
Now then, let us teach you the stylish rules of love.
いい？ 女の子は私だけなの
Got it? I am the only girl for you.
申し訳ございません 貴方の世界には
So sorry, but in your world...
他に1人も居場所なんてあるはずないの
...there's no place for anyone else at all!
誰しもが羨むレベルで愛してよ
Love me to a degree everyone will envy!
思わず真似してみたくなるような
Make it so irresistible that everyone wants to copy us!
恋しよう ねぇ 流行っちゃってる Lovey-dovey 一途ってトレンド
Let's fall in love! Hey, it's trending! Lovey-dovey, being devoted is the trend!
よそ見なんてね Darling-Darling 時代遅れなの
Looking elsewhere, Darling-Darling, is so outdated!
Only One同士よ 好き 好き いつだって私でしょ
We're both each other's Only One! Love you, love you, it's always me, right?
貴方はほら 最先端でいてよ
You, look, stay on the cutting edge!
じゃあ教えてよ 貴方の頭の中
Well then, tell me what's inside your head!
照れくさそうな目も 私のものよ
Even those bashful eyes belong to me!
昔の秘密も 2人にありえないわ
Secrets from the past? Impossible between the two of us!
全てを預けて 隠し事なんて無しのよ
Entrust everything to me, no keeping secrets allowed!
ねぇ 気付いちゃってる Lovey-dovey 素直ってトレンド
Hey, have you noticed? Lovey-dovey, being honest is the trend!
秘密なんてね Darling-Darling 的外れなのよ
Keeping secrets, Darling-Darling, is totally missing the point!
正直同士よ 好き 好き 永遠に結びましょう
We're both honest with each other! Love you, love you, let me tie us together forever!
貴方はほら 最先端でいてよ
You, look, stay on the cutting edge!
どんなときも胸を震わせてね
Make my heart throb no matter when!
離れていてもほら 繋がってる
Even when we're apart, see, we're connected!
そう思って
Keep thinking that way!
こんなに素敵なの
It's so wonderful!
この世のこの世の終わりまで 何から何まで繋ぎましょう
Until the very end of this world, let's link everything together!
私の私の宝物
My, my precious treasure!
そうでしょ そうでしょ
Right? Right?
恋しよう ねぇ 流行っちゃってる Lovey-dovey 一途ってトレンド
Let's fall in love! Hey, it's trending! Lovey-dovey, being devoted is the trend!
よそ見なんてね Darling-Darling 時代遅れなの
Looking elsewhere, Darling-Darling, is so outdated!
Only One同士よ 好き 好き いつだって私でしょ
We're both each other's Only One! Love you, love you, it's always me, right?
貴方はほら 最先端でいてよ 私だけ居てよ
You, look, stay on the cutting edge! Stay only with me!
お願い お願い
Please, please!
私だけよ
Only me!
お願い お願い
Please, please!
私だけ居てよ
Stay only with me!
Ruff ruff!
That was our brand new original song, "Ichizutte Trend"!
私たちのオリジナル曲、「一途ってトレンド」でした！どうだったかな？新曲だよ！
That was our original song, "Ichizutte Trend"! How was it? It's a new song!
It was written and composed by the amazing Ryujin Kiyoshi-san! He's written so many songs for idols and voice actors that we really, really love!
We're so, so honored! Thank you! 作詞作曲は清竜人さんでした！清さんにオリ曲を書いていただけて光栄です！夢みたい！
We're so, so honored! Thank you! Lyrics and composition were by Ryujin Kiyoshi-san! We're so honored to have him write an original song for us! It's like a dream!
And it's our loveliest, doveyest song yet! So you know, we hope you like it lots and lots! And it will be released on digital streaming platforms at midnight JST!
Right after this! この配信のあと0時からデジタルリリースされますので、いっぱい聴いてくれたら嬉しいな！「一途ってトレンド」！
Right after this! It will be digitally released starting at midnight after this stream, so we'd be so happy if you listen to it a lot! "Ichizutte Trend"!
Ruff ruff! That's not all for the announcements!
重大告知だったっけ？
Was it a major announcement?
What do you think, Ruffians?
So excited to have a new song produced by... Not quite! We still have something, huh? Did you want to take a look at it?
So excited to have a new song produced by... Not quite! We still have something, right? Did you want to take a look at it?
Do you wanna know what's the big announcement, Ruffians?
Okay, okay! じゃあ公開！じゃあ公開！ Okay! Here we go! どうぞ！
Okay, okay! Here it comes! Here it comes! Okay! Here we go! Go ahead!
一緒がいい 一緒にいたい ALL TIME Lifetime Showtime
We want to be together, we want to stay together, all time, Lifetime Showtime
ANYTIME BAU BAU 一生涯 SING WITH YOU
Anytime, BAU BAU, for a lifetime, sing with you
めくるめくランデヴー 迷宮で待ってる
A dazzling rendezvous, waiting in the labyrinth
背中に君を感じていたいのお
I want to feel you right behind me
ふわふわ もこもこ 魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Fuwafuwa Mokomoko, Demonic Guard Dog Sisters☆★
この世界に爆誕 “BAU”DOLです
Newly born into this world, we are "BAU"DOLs
私たちFUWAMOCOの1stアルバムの発売が決定いたしましたー！
The release of our FUWAMOCO 1st Album has been officially confirmed!
アルバムタイトルは『FUWAMOCO à la mode 〜いつだってあなたの笑顔を守るのッ〜』！
The album title is "FUWAMOCO à la mode ~forever protecting your smile~"!
ジャケットイラストはイラストレーターの渡辺明夫先生！
The jacket illustration is by illustrator Akio Watanabe-sensei!
FUWAMOCOの憧れの方に描いてもらえることになって、本当に嬉しいです！
We're so happy that someone FUWAMOCO looks up to is drawing it for us!
BAU BAU!
現在制作中のイラストを特別に見せちゃいます！
We're going to show you a special sneak peek of the illustration in progress!
じゃーじゃん！
Ta-da!
今回のアルバムは2枚組で作りました！
We made this album as a 2-disc set!
ディスク1の収録楽曲はなんと11曲！新曲もたくさんです！
Disc 1 features a total of 11 songs! There are lots of new songs too!
ディスク2はAdventのオリジナル曲のFUWAMOCO歌唱バージョンと、アルバムについて語っているアフターパーティーです！
Disc 2 features FUWAMOCO vocal versions of Advent's original songs, plus an after-party talking about the album!
詳細はまだ内緒だから、続報を待っててね！
The details are still a secret, so stay tuned for further updates!
さらにさらに、アルバムにはCD以外のものもたくさん詰め込みました！
On top of that, the album is packed with lots of items besides the CDs!
キラキラステッカーシート、アクスタ、ホロカ、アナザージャケット！
Sparkly sticker sheet, acrylic stand, holo card, and an alternate jacket!
そして2人で心を込めてラフィアンズに向けて書いたお手紙！
And a letter written from our hearts by the two of us for all the Ruffians!
そしてそして、2人で頑張って買ってくれた皆さん全員に直筆サインを書くよー！
And on top of that, we'll work hard to personally sign for everyone who buys one!
私たちの1stアルバム、たくさんの人が聴いてくれたら嬉しいな！
We'd be so happy if lots of people listen to our 1st album!
We have huge news! Our very first album is finally happening!
The title is FUWAMOCO à la mode ~forever protecting your smile~!
The cover illustration is by Akio Watanabe-sensei, an illustrator we've always looked up to! We're so happy he agreed to draw for us!
BAU BAU!
And we want to show you something special right now! The illustration still in progress!
Ta-da!
This album is a two-disc set! Disc 1 has 11 songs, and so many brand new ones!
Disc 2 is FUWAMOCO's own vocal version of Advent's original songs, plus an after-party talking all about the album!
But you know, we can't spill any more details yet, so stay tuned!
And that's not all! The album is packed with more than just the CD!
A sparkly sticker sheet, acrylic stands, holo card, an alternate jacket, and a letter that the two of us wrote from our hearts just for you!
And you know, the two of us are working hard to hand-sign every single copy for everyone who buys one!
We'd be so happy if lots of Ruffians get to listen to our 1st album!
BAU BAU!
BAU BAU! We're so happy!
It's finally here! The album! The album!
ずっと夢を見てたFUWAMOCOのアルバムですよー！
It's the FUWAMOCO album we've always dreamed of!
CD！見て！ほら！CD！CD！ Album got so many... Album! Album! Yeah!
CD! Look! See! CD! CD! Album got so many... Album! Album! Yeah!
Woah! Yeah! This is it! This is the album we always dreamed of, Ruffians!
あ！これモコちゃん… え？光を手に反射… Ruffians, details!
Ah! This, Moco-chan... Huh? Reflecting the light onto her paw... Ruffians, details!
Thank you, Ruffians! Thank you for always supporting us! We're so happy!
いっぱい応援してくれてありがとう！本当、みんなのおかげだよー！
Thank you so much for all your support! It's really thanks to everyone!
It's thanks to you, Ruffians, that we can do all these amazing things!
みんな、本当にありがとう！
Everyone, thank you so much!
Bau bau!
To repeat the important parts for today...
Pre-orders start VERY SOON!
9 PM JST or 5 AM PT!
Yeah, right after this, okay? Right away!
販売は今日21時！
Sales start today at 21:00!
そう、このあとすぐ！から受注開始しまーす！
Right after this! Pre-orders begin!
Yeah! Yeah!
Ah, are you ready? Ready?
And like we mentioned...
Every single CD will be signed by us!
Us!
That's right! With these paws!
Yeah! With these paws!
Yeah! And that's gonna be signed with...
All our heart!
CD全部！この二人から直筆サインがありますよ！
Every CD! With handwritten signatures from us!
Yeah! 書きますよー！
Yeah! We'll sign them!
心を込めて、大切に作ってるアルバムなので、みんなの手元に届いてほしいです！
We put our hearts into making this album, so we want it to reach everyone!
Take home, please!
Yeah!
But this album really means so much to us, so it means everything in the world!
If you could get a copy and add it to your collection, and listen to all the precious songs that we put all our hearts into, all the moments, all the time, okay?
You know, this is the day! The day we've been dreaming of this entire year, so...
Thank you!
Thank you! And, Ruffians, you know, it's not done here yet! No! No!
We'll continue to work really hard on it so it'll be everything that you dreamed of, too, Ruffians, okay?
Yeah!
Thank you, Ruffians!
You're excited? Yeah!
You can get it right after this, okay?
And don't forget! 忘れないでね！
And don't forget! Don't forget, okay?
Yeah!
Well, Ruffians, with that, we'd like to continue to sing two final songs for you today!
And one of the songs is a song by a senpai who we really admire as an idol!
次の曲はアイドルとしてとっても尊敬していた先輩の曲です！
The next song is by a senpai we deeply respected as an idol!
Ruffians, we hope our feelings reach you! Please listen to #あくあ色ぱれっと.
Ruffians, we hope our feelings reach you! Please listen to #AquaColorPalette.
何をしても不器用で 何かとミスしてばっか
No matter what I do, I'm clumsy and keep making mistakes.
ダメダメな私だって できることがあるの
Even a useless person like me has things I can do.
凹んで悲しくたって 笑顔にしてあげるんだ
Even if you're down and sad, I'll make you smile.
ここにいるから早く 私を見つけてね
I'm right here, so hurry and find me!
(love you love you. I love you. love you love you. I love you so much.)
(love you love you. I love you. love you love you.)
愛してもっと
Love me more!
いつでも隣にいるし いつでも一緒に笑える
I'll always be by your side, and we can always laugh together.
私をたくさん知って たくさん好きって言って
Know lots about me, and tell me you love me lots!
ワガママで朝も苦手 ドジだしダメダメだけど
I'm selfish and bad at mornings, clumsy and useless, but...
それでも私のこと 見ててね
Still, please keep watching over me.
描く夢の未来へ続く
Continuing toward the future of our dreams...
道をキミと歩けますように
May I walk this path together with you.
ねぇ もっと！ 好きになってもらいたいの
Hey, more! I want you to love me even more!
頭の中は君ばっか！！
My head is filled with nothing but you!!
っとゆーかそっぽなんて向いてないで！
I mean, don't look away from me!
あぁもう！ ヤキモチしちゃうわ
Ah, geez! I'm getting jealous!
あぁ ずっとずっと好きがいいの
Ah, I want you to love me forever and ever!
心の奥もトキメキちゃうくらいに
So much that my heart throbs deep inside!
こっち向いてよダーリン？
Look over here, darling?
あぁもう離さないから、絶対に！
Ah, I'll never let you go, never!
(love you love you. I love you. love you love you. I love you so much.)
(love you love you. I love you. love you love you.)
君がいるから 私いつでも頑張れるんだ
Because you're here, I can always do my best.
凹んで悲しくたって
Even if I'm down and sad...
君がいるから...
Because you're here...
君がいるから歩いてこれた
Because you were here, I was able to keep walking.
君がいなくっちゃ前も見えない
If you weren't here, I couldn't even see ahead.
嫌なこととかつらいこととか 明日へ
Troubles and painful times, toward tomorrow...
君の力でここまで笑ってこられたんだ
Thanks to your strength, I was able to come this far with a smile.
今度はもっと私がぐっと引っ張って連れて行くんだ
This time, I'll take your hand and lead you even further.
君がいるから私がいるの
Because you're here, I exist.
こんな私を愛してくれて
Thank you for loving someone like me.
ねぇもっと ねぇもっと まだもっと 受け止めてよね
Hey, more, hey, more, accept even more of me, okay?
ねぇいい？
Hey, is that alright?
さあ声を上げて
Come on, raise your voice!
ねぇもっと ねぇもっと 好きになっててもらいたいの
Hey, more, hey, more, I want you to love me even more.
いつでもそう私ばっかり
Why is it always like I'm the only one...
みたいにそっぽ向いて任せないで
Don't just turn away and leave it all to me.
ねぇほら夢中にさせちゃうわ ああ
Hey, look, I'll make you completely head over heels, ah!
ずっとずっと好きで居たいの
I want to love you forever and ever.
過去の君も今の君もそう変わらない
The past you and the present you haven't changed a bit.
こっち向いててよダーリン
Look this way, darling!
あーもう離さないから
Ah, I won't let you go anymore,
絶対に 絶対ね 絶対よ 約束だよ
Absolutely, okay? Absolutely! It's a promise!
愛しちゃうもっと
I'll love you even more!
This next song is our last song!
Let's continue to love Hololive much and more!
いつの間にか見つけてた遠い夢
A distant dream I found before I knew it,
一人じゃ見えなかった景色
scenery that couldn't be seen alone.
波打つ風の音と 加速していく想いに
To the sound of the rippling wind and accelerating feelings,
戸惑いを覚えた
I felt confused.
ずっと追いかけた理想の姿は
The ideal image I've chased for so long
まだ届かなくて遠いけど
is still unreachable and far away, but...
きっとこの瞬間を かけがえのないみんなで
Surely, during this moment, with everyone who is irreplaceable,
共に行くよ！
we'll go together!
手を繋いで
Hand in hand,
3・2・1！
3, 2, 1!
輝き宿して
Harboring brilliance,
夢の場所へ！
to our dream place!
駆け抜けていく 僕たちの青春の光は
Running through, the light of our youth
誰にも止められないよ！
can't be stopped by anyone!
笑い合う分だけ優しく
Just as gently as we laugh together,
零れる涙さえ今
even the spilling tears now,
ほら輝かせ
look, make them shine!
明日へ運ぶから君の隣へ
I'll carry them to tomorrow, right to your side!
僕たちは世界を超えて行く
We will go beyond the world!
迎えに行くよ まだ見えない明日も
I'll come pick you up! Even for a tomorrow not yet visible,
キラメキに変えてきっと
changing it into sparkle, surely
僕たちが未来へと
we will take you...
連れて行くから！
to the future!
背伸びしては手を伸ばす憧れの
Reaching up on tiptoe, stretching towards our admiration,
行き先示す星になろう
let's become the star showing the way.
つまずくその度に 手を差し伸べ合えたら
Every time we stumble, if we can reach out to each other,
すぐに届くはずさ
it should reach us soon.
そっと踏み出した小さな勇気が
The small courage gently taken forward,
もう消えないように繋げよう
let's connect it so it never fades away!
不安も愛しさも大切に抱きしめて
Holding both anxiety and affection dear to our hearts,
共に行くよ！
we'll go together!
目を合わせて
Looking into each other's eyes,
3・2・1！
3, 2, 1!
晴れ渡る希望へ飛び出せるよ！
We can leap out toward clear hope!
突き抜けていく
Breaking through,
僕たちの透き通る決意は
our crystal-clear determination
まだまだ止められないよ！
still can't be stopped!
ありきたりな今日こそ
Turning even an ordinary day today
トキメキに変えてもっと
into excitement and more,
僕たちがいつまでも
because we will always
背中押すから！
push you forward!
Ruffians, we have something we want to share with you!
It's now been three years since we made our debut here in hololive!
There's been so many precious memories made, laughs together...
...and even some tears through rough times, too.
It's been lots of challenges, but it's all been worth it!
All the 22 dreams we talked about three years ago have been coming true one by one!
And now, our dream of our own first full album is coming true, too!
Yeah! We're so grateful and thankful!
We want to continue on this journey no matter what comes our way!
As long as we're together, we know that we can do the impossible!
Thank you for being our precious Ruffians!
Here by our side, we'll continue to protect your smiles forever and ever!
Bow wow!
くだらない日常で描いていた
In the dull everyday life I used to paint,
いつからか過去のライトになって
somehow it became a light from the past.
満たす少しずつ 描ける大好きを紡ぎ
Little by little filling it up, weaving the things I love to paint,
どこまでも高く
reaching endlessly high!
明日色の空へ
Toward the sky colored with tomorrow,
駆け抜けていく
we sprint through!
僕たちの青春の光は
The light of our youth,
誰にも止められないよ
no one can ever stop it!
笑い合う毎日に こぼれる涙さえ
In the days we laugh together, even the spilled tears,
ほら輝かせ 明日へ運ぶから
look, they shine as we carry them into tomorrow.
君の隣へ
To your side,
僕たちは
we will...
世界を超えていく
...soar beyond the world,
迎えに行くよ
and come to meet you!
まだ見えない明日も ひらめきに変えて
Turning even the unseen tomorrow into inspiration,
きっと僕たちが未来へと
surely we will head toward the future!
果てのない未来へと
Toward an endless future,
連れて行くから
we will take you along!
[Thank you for 3 Years!!] It's because of you that we can shine so bright! The diary of memories we've made together these past 3 years means everything to us! - Fuwawa, Mococo
We're looking forward to even more memories in the future! No matter what, we'll continue to become even stronger demon dogs so we can protect your smile furrever and ever! - Fuwawa, Mococo